

Gunawan

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Bandung, Jawa barat 089644572998 gunawanramadhan50@gmail.com Garut, 13 February 1994

ABOUT ME

Hello! I'm a backend developer with 2 more years experience in backend developer and sometimes i was help frontend.

Working for your company I will use all my skills, knowledge from my previous experience, to raise the profit from your company or your product. I'm ready will work with team or individual.

I would appreciate the opportunity to show you how I can help your company meet its goals.

WORK HISTORY

Desember 2020 - Present

PT. Sumber Trijaya Lestari (Alfamart Digital Business)

now I work at Sumber Trijaya Lestari, is a specialized company for digital Alfamart, such as Alfamikro, Alfagift, and Alfatrex, I am here as a backend developer for the Alfamikro project to handle the API with the team.

November 2020 - Januari 2021

PT. Akselerasi Teknologi Investama (Vendor IT)

Currently I'm working as software engineer, where my role is:

- develop applications based on the specified project.
- make detailed program specifications.
- work closely with the team in implementing bug fixes, ensuring application stability

and performance

- helping to program both applications and operating system using a programming language

November 2019 - November 2020

Spinpay (MNC GROUP)

Currently I'm working on product from MNC GROUP that is SPINPAY which is product focused on fintech, I'm working as a backend developer sometimes i help team for deployment for all task teamwork that has passed QA and QC to production, using VM CenTOS.

Agustus 2018 – November 2019

metube.id (MNC GROUP)

I was focused on backend developer sometimes i help team for task frontend from metube.id, which is media platform streaming one of part from largest media MNC GROUP.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2017 Bachelor's degree, Informatic Engineering

Universitas Komputer Indonesia (UNIKOM)

LANGUAGES

English (beginner) - Indonesia

PERSONAL DATA

Name : Gunawan

Place, Date of Birth : Garut, 13 february 1994

Gender : Male

Religion : Moslem

Marital Status : Single

Nationality : Indonesian

KNOWLEDGE & EXPERIENCE

- Golang
- Javascript
- Frontend
- Backend
- Python
- ReactJS

OTHER KNOWLEDGE

- MS Office
- Linux
- · CI/CD
- Clean push/commit to repository
- QRIS
- Database